I'm new to Tokyo
그 아이 도쿄는 처음이니까 말이야
After all, it might have been nice to meet you
역시 마중 나간다고 하는게 좋았을지도
It will be okay ~ I'm not a kid
괜찮을거야~ 애도 아닌데 뭐
I'm worried even if I say that
그렇게 말해도 걱정이야
Miho Don't worry too much ...
미호 너무 걱정하지 말···
-I think I'm here. -Come, come.
- 왔나봐 - 왔다, 왔다
Let's go ~
나가요~
-Come out ~! - sister!!
- 나오야~! - 언니!!
I waited!
기다렸다고!
Thanks
고마워
I was worried ~ I can find it right here
걱정했다고~ 여기 제대로 찾아 올 수 있을지
Nice to meet you
반가워, 이리줘
It's been a long time, I'll be starting today
오랜만이에요, 오늘부터 신세 지겠습니다
What are you doing so hard ~
뭘 그렇게 딱딱하게 구는거니~
I put the room away.
방 치워놨으니까
Thank you
감사합니다
You don't have to say that, come in
그런 말 안해도 돼, 들어와 들어와
Take off your shoes here
신발 여기 벗고
This way, this way
이쪽이야, 이쪽
Isn't that cool?
근사하지?
- Yeah··· - right?
- 네··· - 그렇지?
This way
이쪽이야
Don't refrain
사양하지 말라니까
I mean ~ Are you nervous?
그러니까 말이야~ 긴장이라도 한거니?
Why don't you put your luggage down
짐 내려놓지 그러니
Yes, give me
그래, 이리줘
Put this down
이것도 내려놓고
What is it, why?
뭐야, 왜그러니?
-It's a gift. - Really? Thanks
- 선물이에요 - 정말? 고마워
What is this
뭘까 이거
This is a shop castella near my house, right?
이거 우리 집 근처에 있는 가게 카스테라잖아?
-Did you live on the way? - Huh!
- 오는길에 산거니? - 응!
Wow this is really good ~
우와 이거 정말 맛있는건데~
I want to eat
먹고싶은걸
That's fortunate
다행이네요
Cut or cut?
잘라, 잘라야하나?
Yes
그렇다고
I want to eat quickly
빨리 먹고싶은걸
Yeah, you forgot to eat because you were worried
그러게, 너 걱정하느라 먹는것도 까먹었다고
Sit down, sit down
앉아, 앉으렴
I'm glad ~ I'm getting out of the car
기쁜걸~ 차 내올게
Thank you
아 고마워
Can I help you?
뭔가 도와줄까?
OK
괜찮아
- Really? -Sit down
- 정말? - 앉아 있어
Delicious ~
맛있다~
How did you get to Tokyo?
도쿄엔 어떻게 왔어?
I'm on the tram.
저, 전차 타고 왔지
It took a long time
오래 걸렸겠다
Why aren't you flying?
왜 비행기 안탄거야?
The atmosphere of the city I wanted to feel it
그 뭐랄까 도시의 분위기를 느껴보고 싶다고 생각해서
So you're late?
그래서 늦은거구나?
I sold a little glance
조금 한눈을 팔았었죠
I was really worried Do you know how many hours you waited?
정말 걱정이었다고 몇시간이나 기다린지 아는거니?
Miho continued to worry
미호가 계속 걱정했었다고
You're right, though
제대로 왔잖아 그래도
I'm glad
다행이지
I arrived at my parents well Wouldn't it be nice to contact you?
부모님한테 잘 도착했다고 연락하는게 좋지 않을까?
Are you okay?
괜찮은거야?
I'll do it
내가 할게 내가
I'll listen to you again Don't you want to hear nagging?
또 한소리 들을테니까 잔소리 듣기 싫지?
like that
그렇구나
It's a big deal
큰일이네
Why are you confused?
왜 혼난다는거야?
What are you confused with?
뭘로 혼난다는거야?
When will you get a job?
언제 취직 할거냐 이런거지 뭐
I'm sorry
죄, 죄송해요
You don't have to rush
서두를 필요 없잖아
Any problems?
문제 없지?
I think it's my home You can stay comfortable
자기 집이라고 생각하고 편하게 있어도 되니까
I'm really going to lose weight
정말 신세 좀 질게요
If you find a real room, you will go out right away.
진짜 방 찾으면 바로 나갈테니까요
-Thank you so far. -No, it's okay.
- 그전까지 잘 부탁드려요 - 아니, 괜찮다니까
I don't need to hurry
서두를 필요 없다니까
If you hurry and find a place to live
서둘러서 살 곳을 구하면
fairly···
꽤···
I will regret it
후회할 거라고
Because it's a woman
여자니까
It might be dangerous.
위험할지도 모르고 말이야
If you live on the first floor, strange people may get twisted
1층에 살면 이상한 사람들이 꼬일 수도 있고
Yes, underwear thief.
그래, 속옷 도둑이라던가
Second floor or third floor? I need to find it carefully
2층이냐 3층이냐 이런것도 잘 따져가면서 찾아야 하니까
Until then, you can stay here ...
그전까지는 여기 있어도 되니까 딱히···
I'm sorry
죄송해요
Where is work ...
일은 어디서···
Oh yeah
아, 그래
First of all, it is the most urgent
우선 그게 제일 급하긴 한데
You can take it slowly, step by step.
천천히 한걸음씩 나아가면 되지 뭐
I think it's your home
자기 집이라고 생각해
I'm really sorry
정말 미안해
Don't do that ~
그러지 말라니까~
What does Nao-chan want to do?
나오짱은 뭐 하고 싶은거 있어?
Actually, I wanted to be a cartoonist.
사실은 만화가가 되고 싶었는데요
That···
그···
Now is
지금은
I'm looking for something normal.
평범한 일을 찾으려구요
like that
그렇구나
It's a big deal
큰일이네
-Still, really good - like that
- 그래도 정말 잘그려 - 그렇구나
Do you often draw now?
지금도 종종 그리지?
Huh···
응···
I knew it
그럴줄 알았어
Did you bring it?
가져왔지?
-Show me later -I miss you too
- 나중에 보여줘 - 나도 보고싶은걸
Not really
그정돈 아니에요
Let me guide you through my house
우리 집 안내 좀 해줄게
Huh!
응!
First, here is the bathroom
일단 여기가 욕실이야
- bathroom - okay
- 욕실 - 그래
Bathroom and sink
욕실이랑 세면대
wide
넓다
When I get that bath. The lever is a little bad
그 목욕물 받을때는 말이야 레버가 좀 안좋아서
It's better to turn it on than take it off
벗고 들어가기보단 일단 틀어놓는게 좋을거야
Then you can avoid the cold
그러면 추운걸 좀 피할 수 있을거야
Ok
알았어
Right here ...
여기 바로 옆에···는
-It's a bathroom. -Hwajingsil?
- 화장실이야 - 화징실?
This is my sister ...
언니 이거···
You're using washlet * Japanese Bidet
워슈렛토 쓰는구나 *일본식 비데
okay
그래
That's awesome, I write it once
굉장하다, 이거 한번 쓰면 계속 쓴다는데
I don't know well, I just use what was installed
잘은 몰라, 나도 설치되있던거 그냥 쓰는거라
This ...
이거 그···
-Can you wipe your ass? -Yes
- 엉덩이도 닦을 수 있는거지? - 그렇다고
You can use it, but be careful when you use it
써도 되는데 쓸때 조심해
In the first too strong century You may not be able to adapt
처음에 너무 강한 세기에 적응 못할수도 있으니까
Yes, I might be surprised In the beginning, it would be better to use a weak setting.
그래, 깜짝 놀랄지도 모르니까 처음에는 약한 설정으로 하는게 좋을거야
- weak? -Yes, with weak strength
- 약한? - 그래 약한 세기로
If you don't press the stop button Be careful because it may turn into the water of the bathroom
다 끝나고 정지버튼 안누르면 화장실 물바다가 되버릴 수도 있으니까 조심하고
like that
그렇구나
I have never used it
써본적이 없어서
Ok
알았어
Write carefully
조심해서 써
restroom
화장실
Next is Nao's room.
다음은 나오 방이야, 방은 이쪽~
Here is the room
여기가 나오 방이야
This is the original guest room. There will be no inconvenience in writing
여긴 원래 손님방이라 쓰는데 불편한건 없을거야
Yes, thank you
응, 고마워
Wide ~
넓다~
so?
그러니?
Is the room good?
방 좋지?
Wow, you have a bed.
와, 침대도 있구나
If you have any difficulties Should I talk properly?
뭐 곤란한거 있으면 제대로 얘기해야 한다?
Huh
응
Then this is a spare key ~
그럼 이건 스페어 키~
Thanks
고마워
Can't we lose it?
잃어버리면 안된다?
Ok
알았어
Then I'm going to go cook I'll call you when it's done
그럼 언니 밥하러 가볼테니까 다되면 부를게
-I've been resting until now. - Huh!
- 그전까지 푹 쉬고 있어 - 응!
No way ...
안돼에··!
Is it a lie?
거짓말이지?
Sister ...?
언니가··?
out? I'm not going to eat?
나오? 안먹어?
Yes, I'll eat well
응, 잘 먹을게
Nao, your face looks bad. Where is it not good?
나오, 얼굴이 안좋아 보이는데 어디 안좋아?
no
아니야
I'm just trying to sleep
잠을 설친거 뿐이야
Sorry, were you noisy?
미안, 시끄러웠니?
Huh? what?
응? 뭐가?
Maybe you heard something strange?
뭐 이상한 소리라도 들은거 아닐까?
There is no sound
못하는 소리가 없어
Gee, it's time to go
이런, 갈 시간이야
thank you
땡큐
What time are you coming today?
오늘 몇시쯤에 올거야?
I'm going to be a little late because I have an accounting today.
오늘 회계 업무가 있어서 좀 늦을거야
Don't take my share
내 몫은 차리지 마
Okay, then I'll eat out with Nao.
알았어, 그럼 난 나오랑 외식할게
Nao, are you okay?
나오, 괜찮지?
Huh··
응··
Then I will go.
그럼 다녀올게
Bye
잘 다녀와
Bye···
다녀오세요···
You can go crazy, so give me more
미쳐버려도 좋으니까 더 박아줘
No, go away!
안돼 가버려어··!
It's gone ...! Wait
가버렸다고··! 잠깐
More ...!
더··!
Oh no!
안된다고오오!
Wait a minute
잠깐만
Go away again!
또 가버려어어!
I can't ...
안된다니까··
I'm gone
갔단 말이야
No, no more ...
안돼 더이상은··
No way ...
안돼에··!
I'm really like a pervert ...
정말 변태 같다니까아··
No, I can't ...
안된다니까앗···
I'm going to lose this ...
이거 빠져버리 겠는걸···
The fierce sex life of a married sister The sister-in-law I witnessed had lust ...
결혼한 언니의 격렬한 성생활을 목격한 처제가 욕정을 해서···
Sunday 11:00 AM
일요일 오전 11시
Honey?
여보?
I had yakisoba for lunch, okay?
점심으로 야키소바 해놨는데 괜찮지?
Uh, good
어, 좋아
Then I will go.
그럼 다녀올게
Go ~
다녀와~
What's the stock again?
뭐야 또 주식이 떨어졌네
What are you waiting for ?!
잠깐 뭐야?!
Nao, what is Nao-chan doing?
나오, 나오짱 뭐하는거야?
Stop, stop
그만, 그만
What are you doing?
나오 뭐하는거야?
What's going on ...
뭐야, 무슨 일이···
Wait a minute
잠깐만
Why do you do that, calm down ...
왜 그러는거야, 진정해··· 읍
What's what what's doing, stop stop stop
뭐야 뭐야 뭐하는, 그만 그만 그만
Such a place ...
그런곳을··
No ... Nao-chan doesn't work.
안돼·· 나오짱 안된다니까
What is this?
이게 무슨··?
Gee, calm, calm down
지, 진정, 진정해
What, what
뭐니, 뭐야
Stop, stop
그만, 그만해
awhile
잠깐
When I come back, what do I do when I come back
돌아오면, 돌아오면 어쩌려고
No
안된다고
It's not there
거긴 안되는데
Nao-chan?
나오짱?
Why is it ...
왜 그러는··· 하앙
No
안되는데
No, no, no
안돼, 안돼 읍
No no ...
안돼 안되는데··
I'll put it
넣을게요
Gee, calm, calm down
지, 진정, 진정해
Calm down
진정해
What x5
뭐하는 x5
No, no
안돼, 안된다니까
Difficult to find ...
들키면 곤란···
No wait
잠깐 안돼
No no no
안돼 안돼 안돼
It's awesome ... It feels so good.
굉장해··· 이렇게 기분 좋은거였구나
I can't ...
안된다니까···
No, I feel good ...
안되는데 기분 좋아···
I feel good
기분 좋앗··
I like it so much ...
너무 좋아아···
No
안돼
Good mood
기분 좋아
You can't move like that ...
그렇게 움직이면 안돼··
Ok
좋아앗··
I love it here ...!
여기가 너무 좋아··!
What are you doing?
뭐하는··?
This is a little dangerous
이거 좀 위험한데
Gandaad ...
간다앗··
Gandat ...
간닷··
Insertion saying no ...
안된다고 삽입은···
I fell in love with this
이거에 빠져버렸어요
What's really real?
뭐야 진짜 진짜얍·· 읍··
I feel good ...
기분 좋아앙··
No···
안돼···
It's intense ... it's intense!
격렬해·· 격렬하다고!
No ... it's too intense
안돼·· 너무 격렬하다고
Good mood··
기분 좋아··
No
안되는데
That's not possible ...!
그건 안된다니까··!
It's too bad!
너무 좋아서 안돼!
I feel good
좋아·· 기분 좋아앗
Go away ... Ganda ...
가버려·· 간다·· 간다앗
I'm gone again ...
또 가버려엇··
No
안되는데
No, that's ...
안된다니까 그건···
I feel good
기분 좋아앗
More ... more
더·· 더요
Put it in ...
넣어줘요···
Put it in ...?
넣어달라고··?
I can't
안된다니까
I'll be back soon ...
곧 돌아올거라고···
Touch your butt
엉덩이 만져줘요
Go away ... Ganda ... Gandaat ...
가버려·· 간다·· 간다앗··!
Really come out ...!
정말 나와·· 나와버린다고!
Stop now, let's stop?
이제 그만, 그만하자?
Miho will be back, so come back ...
미호가 돌아올 거라니까, 돌아올··
Wait, I'm really coming back
잠깐만, 정말로 돌아올 거라니까
Touch me ...
만져줘요···
Do you feel good?
기분 좋죠?
It feels good, but it really doesn't work.
기분·· 기분 좋긴 한데 안된다고 정말
-I'm coming back. - It's okay
- 돌아올 거라니까 - 괜찮아요
I'll be back, I'll be back ...
돌아올, 돌아올 거라니까···
It's okay, so be quiet
괜찮으니까 조용히 해요
Now, you can see it well ...?
자, 여기 잘 보이죠··?
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
So good
너무 좋앗
I feel good here
여기가 기분 좋아앗
It feels good ...?
기분 좋죠··?
Good but not good
좋긴 하지만 안된다고오···
It's still erection.
계속 풀발기 상태네요
No ...
안돼·· 안된다니까
Then it will be cheap
그러면 싸버릴 거야
What ~?
뭐를요~?
Yes ~? I can't hear you ~?
네~? 안들리는데요~?
I really can't ...
정말 안된다니까··!
Would you like to put it in?
넣어 줬으면 하죠?
Good··
좋아··
I love it!
너무 좋아앗!
No ... Stop it
안돼·· 그만해
Move it ...
움직여줘요···
Kanda ... Kanda ...
간다·· 간다·· 간다앗
I feel good ...
기분 좋다고···
I feel good ... I'll be cheap again
기분 좋아··· 또 싸버릴거야
I feel good
기분 좋다고
Feel better ...
더 기분 좋게··!
No, it'll be really cheap
안돼, 그러면 진짜 싸버릴거라고
Good mood··
기분 좋아··
I feel good ...
기분 좋다고···
More ... more!
더·· 더요!
I really can't because it's cheap
싸버린다니까 정말 안돼
More ... more ... more!
더·· 더요·· 더요!!
I feel good
좋아·· 기분 좋아앗
You can't really touch the nipples there ...
젖꼭지는 진짜 만지면 안돼 거기는··!
Good
좋으면서
You like this
이거 좋아 하잖아요
Go ... go again
간다·· 또 가버려요
go away··
가버려··
Kanda ... Kandaat ...
간다·· 간다앗··
I can't do that
그거 안된다니까
I feel good ...
기분 좋다고···
Do you feel good?
기분 좋아요?
Go again
또 가버려요
Go away ...!
가버려요··!
No more ... No more!
더이상은·· 더이상은 무리야!
It's okay ...
괜찮으니까···
Good ... so good
좋아·· 너무 좋앗
more··
더··
It's the limit ...!
한계야··!
Cheap ··!
싼다··!
No no
안돼 안돼
I really can't
정말 안된다니까
Hide it from your sister and enjoy it with me ♥
언니한테 숨기고 나랑 즐겨요 ♥
Stop stop
그만 그만해
I'm here ~
나 왔어~
This is dangerous ...
이런 위험해··!
It's really difficult, difficult!
정말 곤란해 곤란하다고!
This way
이쪽, 이쪽으로
Here it comes
나오는 여기 있어
I can't
나는 안되지
I'm here ~
나 왔어~
What are you doing?
뭐하고 있어?
No, just···
아니 그냥···
What did you do in that way?
그런 차림으로 뭐한거야?
That's a little exercise ...
그 뭐야 좀 운동을···
Exercise?
운동?
Don't wear panties
팬티 차림으로 하지 말라고
You can eat first
나오 먼저 먹어도 돼
Huh
응
Monday 8:00 AM Honey? In the next 10 minutes Lunch box is ready, can you wait a minute?
월요일 오전 8시 여보? 앞으로 10분 정도면 도시락 준비 되니까 좀만 기다릴래?
Monday 8:00 AM yea, I got it
월요일 오전 8시 응, 알았어
Oh, thanks
아, 고마워
Honey, is it too late today?
여보, 오늘도 늦어?
Uh yeah maybe
으, 응 아마도
I think it will be late
늦을거 같아
What about Bob?
밥은 어쩔래?
I'll be rough
대충 때울게
Ok
알았어
Today's packed lunch
오늘 도시락 두둑히 쌌어
Ah, thank you
아, 땡큐
Three people on the next holiday Where will you go?
다음 휴일에 3명이서 어디 나가지 않을래?
Is there somewhere you want to go?
어디 가고 싶은곳이라도 있어?
Where should I be ...
어디가 좋을까···
Do you think it's a zoo or something?
도, 동물원 이라던가, 괜찮지 않을까
Zoo?
동물원?
Yeah, it's been a while since
그러게, 최근 안간지 좀 됐으니까
- what? - Yes?
- 어라? - 으, 응?
Coming out?
나오는?
Come out, come out, maybe toilet
나오, 나오는 화··화장실·· 간거 아닐까
Oh, the bathroom
아, 화장실
Ah!
아!
Today's egg roll is a little bit fresh but is it okay?
오늘 계란말이 맛이 좀 싱거운데 괜찮겠어?
Yes
으, 응
OK
괜찮아
Must I eat everything?
꼭 다 먹고 와야한다?
Yes
으, 응
Packed lunch
도시락 다 쌌어
-Did you wait ~? - thank you
- 기다렸지~? - 땡큐
Oh, I'll be late
아, 이런 지각하겠어
-Let's go. -Ok
- 그, 그만 가볼게 - 알았어
what? out
어라? 나오
You got it in your mouth
입에 묻었잖니
Lunch box
여기 도시락
Goodbye ~
잘 다녀와~
Bye
다녀오세요
8:00 PM on the same day
같은 날 오후 8시
I'm here
나 왔어
Miho?
미호?
welcome
어서오세요
What are you doing?
뭐하는··?
What is that outfit
뭐야 그 차림은
What what what what
뭐야 뭐야 뭐야
My sister is eating with her friends
언니는 친구들이랑 밥 먹고 온데요
No what is that
아니 뭐냐 그거
It's Miho
미호거잖아
No
안된다고
I really can't
진짜 안된다니까
Do you want to see more?
더 보고 싶어요?
No, you can see it all
아니 다 보여, 훤히 보이잖아
Miho ~
미호~
So there is no
그러니까 없다니까요
- Really? - Huh!
- 진짜야? - 응!
Good job
일 수고하셨어요
Thank you
고맙···긴 한데 잠깐
Because it shouldn't be decorated
꾸겨지면 안되니까요
No, it's okay.
아니 됐어, 됐다니까
Why is that?
왜 그러는거야?
Stop it
그만하렴
I can see it all
다 보인다니까
Put it in front of your hand
손 앞으로 내밀어 보세요
What are you trying to do?
뭐하려고?
awhile··?
잠깐··?
done!
됐다!
No no wait, what is what
아니 아니 잠깐, 뭐야 뭐야
Live it
만세 해보세요
Wait, Nao-chan
잠깐, 나오짱
Let's stop
그만하자
Miho, Miho will come back ...
미호, 미호가 돌아올·· 읍
It's a big deal if it comes to Miho.
미호한테 들키면 큰일이라고
If you do this at the front door because you can't wait for a while ...
잠깐 안된다니까 현관에서 이러면···
Keep quiet
조용히 해요
You're a little sweaty
땀 좀 나셨네요
I can't
안된다니까
Good···
좋아···
No
안돼 거긴
No way
나오짱 안돼
I feel good
기분 좋다고·· 아앗
I will continue
계속 할게요
Oh wait
아, 잠깐
I'm gonna tell you I can't.
안된다니까 들킬거야
I'm going to be caught
들킬거라고
It will smell
냄새 날텐데
The smell of sweat is mandibular ...
땀 냄새가 하악···
where··
어디··
No no no
안돼 안돼 안돼
Why are you in an erection state?
왜 풀발기 상태에요?
Nao-chan, isn't it dirty?
나오짱, 더럽지 않아?
Delicious ~?
맛있는걸요~?
How many times did you go to the bathroom today?
오늘 화장실 몇번이나 갔어요?
I don't know that
그런거 모른다고
I think it tastes like pee
뭔가 오줌맛이 나는거 같기도 하고
I can't ...
안된다니까···
I feel good
기분 좋다고
Will you free your hands?
손 자유롭게 해줄까요?
I want to move
움직이고 싶어
Let's stop now
이제 그만하자
This kind of fire
이런 불장난은
You're a good kid because you're caught by Miho?
미호한테 들킨다니까, 착한 아이지?
then
그럼
I'll release it, so put it in
풀어 줄테니까 넣어줘요
No
안돼
No, I'm going to be caught by Miho.
안된다니까, 미호한테 들킬거라고
Let's talk, let's talk
얘기하자, 얘기나 하자
I hate it!
뭐야 싫어요!
Now, wait
자, 잠깐
What are you doing ?!
뭐뭐뭐 뭐하려고?!
With this good thing ...
이 좋은걸로···
I want to go like a sister too
나도 언니처럼 뿅 가고 싶다구요
here? Come out
여기서? 잠깐 나오
I'm caught by Miho.
미호한테 들킨다니까
I came in ...
들어왔어··
No no
안돼 안된다니까
Nao-chan ...
나오짱···
I feel good ...
기분 좋아앗···
Do it violently like you did to your sister!
언니한테 하던것처럼 격렬하게··· 해줘요!
stop···
그만···
Good···
좋아···
I feel good
기분 좋다고
No··
안돼··
Good mood
기분 좋아
If you don't be quiet, you will hear it.
조용히 안하면 들릴거라구요
So good
너무 좋앗
No go away
안돼 가버려
Go away
가버려요
Gandaat
간다앗
No···
안돼···
No, no more
안된다니까, 더는 안돼
more··!
더··!
backwards···
뒤로···
-Do it from behind -Are you satisfied or not satisfied?
- 뒤에서 해줘요 - 만족, 만족 못한거야?
awhile··!
잠깐··!
From behind ~!
뒤~에서요~!
Quickly
빨리요
I can't do that
그거 안된다니까
Really?
정말?
I'm serious?
진심이야?
Yes, fast.
응, 빨리요
Hot
뜨거워
Kiss me like you do to your sister
언니한테 하는것처럼 키스해 줘요
I love it
너무 좋아앗
What, don't stop!
뭐에요, 멈추지 말아요!
What are you doing
뭐해요
more··!
더··!
I feel good ...
기분 좋아···앙
Kanda ... go away again!
간다·· 간다앗 또 가버려··!
Awesome, this is really ...
굉장해, 이거 정말···
What is it and why?
뭐에요, 왜 그래요··?
In this place ...
이런곳에서···
That's more intense with you.
그야 언니랑은 더 격렬하게 하잖아요
This is so good ··!
이거 너무 좋아요··!
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
Let's stop
그만하자
why··? I do not like it!
왜요··? 싫어요!
I can't
안된다니까
Hate··!
싫어··!
Calm down ... Calm down Nao-chan
진정·· 진정해 나오짱
Knowing ...
알면서··!
awhile···
잠깐···
Hey, are you feeling good?
저기, 기분 좋죠?
It feels good ...
기분 좋긴 한데에··
So good
너무 좋아앙
here··!
여기가··!
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
more··
더··
More ... more!
더·· 더요!
More!
더요!
Kanda ... Kanda ... Kanda ...
간다·· 간다·· 간다·· 간다앗
I can't ...
안된다니까···
Do you feel like turning around like this?
이렇게 빙글빙글 돌리는거 기분 좋죠?
Violent ...
격렬해···
Please stab it more ...!
더 찔러줘요··!
More ...
더요··!
Yes
으··응
Stab me ...
찔러줘요··
more··!!
더··!!
Let's stop
그만하자
It's time to come back.
이제 진짜 돌아올 시간이잖아
I'm not going to come back.
돌아올거니까 안된다고
It's lustful ...
음탕하구나··
If you move like that ...!
그렇게 움직이면··!
It feels good
그거 기분 좋다고
Rubbing like this ...
이렇게 비비는거··
Do you feel so good?
그렇게 기분 좋아요?
I feel so good
엄청 기분 좋다고
More intense!
더 격렬하게요!
I'm going to be cheap
나오 이러다 싸겠어
Then stab me more ♫
그럼 더 찔러줘요 ♫
I think it will be soon
곧 쌀거 같다고
I'll be cheap
싸버릴거야
Nao-chan, I can't.
나오짱 안돼, 그거 안된다고
It's cheap ...
싸버린다고···
Is this ...?
이거·· 이거요?
No, it's really cheap
안돼 진짜 싸버린다니까
Like this ~?
이렇게요~?
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
I love it so much ... more intensely!
너무 좋아·· 더 격렬하게요··!
Like that ...
그렇게요··
It looks like rice ...
쌀거같다고···
It's really cheap
정말 쌀거같다고
good···
좋아요···
It's cheap ...
싼다·· 쌀거야
It's going to be rice
쌀거라고
Do you feel good?
기분 좋죠?
It's really good ...
엄청 좋다고···
Really cheap ...!
진짜 싼다··!
I like it ... I feel good ...
좋아·· 기분 좋아앗···
Cheap ··!
싼다··!
Nao-chan is in trouble
나오짱 곤란하다고
If Miho gets caught in a place like this,
이런곳에서 미호에게 걸리기라도 하면
This one, change it
이, 일단 갈아입자 이거
This is Miho
이거 미호거잖아
It's Miho, so take a shower
미호거니까, 샤워도 하고
What are you really doing ...
정말 뭐하자는 건지···
Tuesday 9pm
화요일 오후 9시
Huh?
응?
What are you so surprised at?
뭘 그리 깜짝 놀라?
Miho ...
미호··
What, why are you so surprised
뭐야, 왜 그리 놀라냐고
no
아니야
-Can I go in together? - Good
- 같이 들어가도 되지? - 좋아
come in
들어와
Why are you so surprised?
왜 그렇게 놀란 거냐구?
What?
뭔데?
What happened?
무슨 일 있었어?
It's nothing
아무것도 아니라니까
Then I'm glad
그럼 다행이지만
What is Nao-chan doing?
나오짱은 뭐해?
out?
나오?
Isn't it in the room?
방에 있지 않을까?
like that
그렇구나
Why?
왜?
No, just···
아니 그냥···
Strange ~?
이상한데~?
No, there's nothing strange
아니야 이상한거 없어
Nothing
아무것도 아니야
- I feel good -Yes ~
- 기분 좋다 - 그러게~
I want to go to a hot spring
온천 가고싶다
I really want to go
진짜 가고 싶은걸
It's a hot spring ...
온천이라···
It's been a while
간지 좀 됐으니까
Should I go on vacation?
휴가 내고 한번 갈까?
Come with me
같이 가자
OK
그러자
I feel tired?
피곤해?
Huh
응
okay
그래
Hot
뜨겁네
Is it hot?
뜨거워?
Did you soak for too long?
너무 오래 몸을 담갔나?
- OK? - Huh
- 괜찮아? - 응
I must go out
슬슬 나가야겠어
okay
그래
I'll go out
나가볼게
Will you come with Miho more?
미호는 좀 더 하고 올거지?
Huh
응
No, there it is
안돼 저기 있다니까
Shit ~
쉬잇~
Nao-chan ...
나오짱···
I can't
안된다니까
Honey, what are you doing there?
여보 거기서 뭐하는거야?
Oh, no, nothing
아, 아니 아무것도 안하는데
Are you okay?
괜찮은거지?
Uh yeah, just body
으, 응 그냥 몸··을
I'm brushing, I'm brushing
닦고 있어, 닦고 있어
Now, now, wait a minute
자,자,잠깐만
Let's go
나가자
Come this way
이쪽으로
Come on
이리 와
Why?
왜?
Now, you can't wait, Miho has it.
자,잠깐 안된다고, 미호가 있잖아
This is really dangerous
정말 이거 위험하다고
With such a lofty look ...
그런 하늘하늘한 차림으로···
That's hot
불끈불끈 하다고
I feel good
기분 좋다고
No
안된다고
I'll lick it a lot
잔뜩 핥아버릴거니까
Didn't you stop saying it?
그만하라고 해도 그만 안했었지?
I have to punish you.
벌을 줘야겠어
Suck it like that
그렇게 빨아봐 입으로
I'll be fine ...
벌울 줄테니까···
I feel good
기분 좋아앗··
Do you want to suck the nipples?
젖꼭지 빨아줄까?
Huh···
응···
Should I take it out
밖으로 꺼내볼까나
Keep collecting like that
계속 그렇게 모으고 있어봐
It's good to touch it like that ...
그렇게 만지면 좋아서···
Do you feel good? It became slippery
기분 좋아요? 미끌미끌 해졌어요
I feel good
기분 좋다고
If not, then
안되는데 그러면
It's slippery
미끌미끌 하네요
more··
더··
more··!
더··!
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
What are you going to do
뭐야 뭐야 뭐하려고
I'm embarrassed for a moment (haha)
잠깐 부끄러운데 (ㅎㅎ)
This posture is a bit shy
이 자세는 좀 부끄러워
Are you ashamed?
부끄러워요?
No
거긴 안돼
Where are you going?
어디가요~?
Wet
젖었어요
Awesome
굉장해
No no
안돼 안돼
Ashamed
부끄럽다고
No
안된다고
Make me wash
빨게 해줘
- it's delicious? -It tastes good
- 맛있어요? - 맛나지
Quickly ...
빨리요···
Do you want to suck?
빨아줬으면 좋겠어?
I feel good ...
기분 좋앗···
Awesome ...
굉장해엣··
More ...
더요···
there··!
거기··!
Like that ...
그렇게 할짝할짝···
I feel good ··! that··
기분 좋아요··! 그거··
awhile··!
잠깐··!
Kanda ...
간다··간다앗
Go away ...!
가버려요··!
Good mood
기분 좋아
I'm so good
너무 잘하는걸
I feel good
기분 좋다고
I can't stand
서있질 못하겠네
I feel bad
안돼 기분 좋다고
I like it ...
좋다고···
Stimulation too ...
자극이 너무···
No more ...
더는 안된다고···
No wait
안돼 잠깐만
If you move so violently ...
그렇게 격렬하게 움직이면···
What is it?
뭐가요~?
You shouldn't be moving so violently
그렇게 격렬하게 움직이면 안된다고
Maybe it's rice?
쌀까봐요?
But it feels good!
그치만 기분 좋으면서!
Violent
격렬해··
If you do it violently, it will be cheap.
그렇게 격렬하게 하면 싸버리니까 안돼··!
It feels so good ...
엄청 기분 좋다고···
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
Do you feel good?
기분 좋아요?
With that bridge ...
그 다리로··
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
I feel good
기분 좋다고
Something's tangled.
뭔가 구슬이 탱탱해 졌어요
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
It's really dirty
엄청 야하다고
Then with your heart
그럼 가슴으로
Is this good?
좋죠 이거?
Good···
좋아···
Do you feel good?
기분 좋아요?
The waist is arbitrary ...
허리가 멋대로···
Waist moves
허리가 움직여
Okay even if you move ...
좋아요 움직여도···
Do you feel good?
기분 좋아요?
Feel better ··!
더 기분 좋아지세요··!
No, then it's cheap. No!
안돼, 그러면 싸버리니까 안돼··!
It's okay, it's okay to be cheap!
괜찮아요, 싸도 괜찮다구요!
No, it's cheap ...!
안돼 싸버린다고··!
No
안돼
Then you can't
그러면 안된다고
Awesome ...
굉장해···
The slippery thing ...
미끌미끌한게···
Is it slippery?
미끌미끌 하죠?
Did you just feel good?
방금거 기분 좋았죠?
It was good ...
좋았어··· 엄청
Do you want to put it?
넣고 싶어요?
I want to put
넣고 싶어
I came in
들어왔어요
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
It feels so good ...
엄청 기분 좋다고···
this···
이거···
Slippery
미끌미끌해
It's hot, it's hot
뜨거워, 뜨겁다고
Is it hot?
뜨거워요?
I'll make it hotter
더 달아오르게 해줄게요
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
Where is it good?
어디가 좋은데요··?
The pussy feels good ...
보지가 기분 좋아···
Are you going here?
여기가요?
Violent
격렬해··
Good mood
기분 좋아
If you keep sticking there
거기만 계속 찌르면
here?
여기?
No go away
안돼 가버려··요
Go right away
바로 가버려요
Go away
가버리라고
awhile··
잠깐··
Kanda ...
간다·· 간다앗
I feel good
기분 좋다고
The nipple feels good ...
젖꼭지가 기분 좋아···
That movement is good
좋다고 그 움직임
Do you feel good?
기분 좋아요?
Which sister feels better with you?
언니랑··· 어느쪽이 더 기분 좋아요?
-That's a little ... -Which way?
- 그건 좀··· - 어느쪽이에요?
-How to do it -Which way!
- 그걸 어떻게 - 어느쪽이에요!
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
awhile··
잠깐··
Kanda ... Kandaah!
간다·· 간다앗!
Go away!
가버려욧··!
You're moving freely!
멋대로 움직이다니욧!
I feel good ...
기분 좋아서···
Do you feel good about me?
내 보지 기분 좋죠?
See you?
언니 보다?
Good···
좋아···
Then you can do more
그럼 더 해도 좋아요
I feel good
기분 좋다고
Is it so good?
그렇게 좋아요?
I love it
무지 좋아앗··
I feel good ...
기분 좋다고···
good?
좋아요?
Deep ...
깊숙이··
Do you feel good inside?
안쪽 기분 좋죠?
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
I feel good ...
기분 좋앗···
more···
더···
Go away ... wait
가버려요·· 잠깐
Go away again ... Go away!
또 가버려·· 가버렷!
Gandaat
간다앗
I feel good
기분 좋다고
-Show me your ass. -Butt?
- 엉덩이 보여줘 - 엉덩이요?
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
Stick me more ...
더 찔러줘요··
more··!
더··!
Kanda ... Kanda ...
간다·· 간다·· 간닷
Go away again!
또 가버려엇!
I feel good
기분 좋앗··
more···
더···
It feels so good ...
엄청 기분 좋다고···
Wait a minute··
잠깐만··
more··
더··
More!
더요!
More ... more!
더요·· 더요!
more··!
더··!
More ... x5
더요··! x5
If you add, it will be cheap
더하면 싸버릴거라고
It's okay
싸두 괜찮은데에
Really?
정말?
Come here
이리와봐
Come this way
이쪽으로
I feel so good
엄청 기분 좋다고
I love it ...
너무 좋앗···
Why··?
왜··?
more··!
더··!
Don't stop
멈추지 마요
continue··!
계속··!
I feel good
기분 좋아앗
I like it so much ...
너무 좋아···
Kanda ... Kanda ...
간다·· 간다·· 간다앗
Kanda ... Kanda ... Go again!
간다·· 간다·· 또 간다앗!
I feel good
기분 좋다고
Go away
가버려어
Gandaat
간다앗
I can't do it anymore
더는 안되겠어
No go away ... go away!
안돼 가버려·· 가버려요!
Go away ... Ganda ... Gandaat ...
가버려·· 간다·· 간다앗··!
Good mood···
기분 좋아···
I feel good
기분 좋다고
there··
거기··
here?
여기?
There ...
거기요··!
Goes··
간다··
Kanda ... Kanda ...
간다·· 간다·· 간다아앗
Good mood··!
기분 좋아··!
Quickly ...
빨리요···
So good
너무 좋아앙
If it stops
안되요 멈추면
Moreover ...
더어···
Wait ... Nadu ...
잠깐·· 나두··
Make her go like I did to my sister!
언니한테 한것처럼 뿅가게 해줘요!
More ... more!
더·· 더요!
Kanda ... Kanda ... Kandaat!
간다·· 간다·· 간다앗!
Awesome ...
굉장한걸···
more?
더?
More vigorously?
더 격렬하게?
-Can you see it going in? -I see ...
- 들어가는거 보이지? - 보여··요
I fell in love
빠져버렸네
Would you like to put it in
넣어볼래?
I see it!
보여요··!
Are you going?
갈거같아?
Are you going to go again?
또 갈거같아?
Click here ...
여기를···
Gandat ...
간닷··
Let's go ... Go!
간다·· 가버렷!
Go away
가버려··엇
more···
더···
It looks like rice
쌀거같다고
It's really good
엄청 좋다고
more··
더··
More ... More ... More!
더·· 더·· 더·· 더요!
I'm gone again ...
또·· 또 가버려엇··
Go again ...
또 가버려··
Kanda ...
간다·· 간다앗
go away··
가버려··
Go away again
또 가버려어
Wait ... Gandaah!
잠깐·· 간다앗!
Wait ... wait
잠깐·· 잠깐
Go away again
또 가버려엉
I can't
안되겠어
It's going to be cold
쌀거야
Cheap ··!
싼다··!
No more
더는 안돼
Sleepy
졸려
what?
어라?
Is something wet?
뭔가 젖지 않았어?
is it?
그런가?
Why is it so wet?
왜 이렇게 젖은거지?
Is it because I'm a little ill
몸이 좀 허해서 그런가
I have some cold sweat ...
식은땀도 좀 나고···
OK?
괜찮아?
Isn't it hot?
좀 덥지 않아?
Yes, it's hot
응, 덥긴 한데
Sleep fast
빨리 자자
okay
그래
Something sloppy ...
뭔가 질척질척···
Well, you can run the washing machine tomorrow.
뭐 내일 세탁기 돌리면 되겠지